rohos.com 2007-12-25

# Rohos Welcome. Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Software  
Our software does not collect any personal information. 

E-mail addresses  
We (Teslain) collects e-mail addresses from users who buy our software. These e-mails are used to send Registrations Keys and news about new versions (major versions). Registered users can change or remove their e-mail addresses by contacting us.

If you sign up for our newsletter, your email address will be kept confidential, and it will only be used to send you our newsletter.

Personal Information  
During purchase process, we collect user information. This information is collected by our registration provider — [Emetrix](http://emetrix.com/cs/) USA based e-commerce company, known for their long-term reputation for professionalism and security. They have their own [Emetrix Privacy & Security](http://www.emetrix.com/company/privacy.asp) statement. No personal information will ever be shared with another company.

We do not even know users' credit card information — this data is only available to the secure service of Emetrix and they deal with it safely.

Product Return Policy (refund)

You can return program for a full refund within a 30 days after purchase. Always contact us for return authorization before returning any item. 

You may not return a product with the following conditions:

Product has been installed and all features works as it described on our web site. If it doesn't work or you encountered an error you should contact us and describe a problem. Then you can ask for an update/fix or refund. 

Sincerely,  
Teslain team.
